Guide to the American Song Sheets Collection, circa 1830s-1920s, bulk 1850s-1880s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- American Song Sheets, circa 1850s-1880s, (4 boxes, items 1-1608)
  - Johnny, Fill Up the Bowl! (Box 1, Item 413)
  - Jordan is a Hard Road to Travel. No. 6 (Box 1, Item 414)
  - Just After the Battle (Box 1, Item 415)
  - Just After the Battle, Mother (Box 1, Item 416)
  - Just Before the Battle, Mother (Box 1, Item 417)
  - Battle Cry of the Pennsylvania Reserves (Box 1, Item 418a)
  - Keystone Brigade (Box 1, Item 418b)
  - King Cotton (Box 1, Item 419)
  - Sinking of the Pirate Alabama (Box 1, Item 420)
  - Little Sogers (Box 1, Item 421)
  - The March of the Maryland Men (Box 1, Item 422)
  - March of the New-York Volunteers (Box 1, Item 423)
  - March On for the Union (Box 1, Item 424)
  - Marching Along (Box 1, Item 425)
  - Marching Along (Box 1, Item 426)
  - Maryland (Box 1, Item 427)
  - Maryland (Box 1, Item 428)
  - Maryland. A Fragment (Box 1, Item 429)
  - Maryland. A Fragment (Box 1, Item 430)
  - The Maryland Battle Cry (Box 1, Item 431)
  - Maryland in Chains (Box 1, Item 432)
  - Maryland, My Home (Box 1, Item 433)
  - Maryland, My Home (Box 1, Item 434)
  - Maryland, My Maryland (Box 1, Item 435)
  - Maryland, My Maryland! (Box 1, Item 436)
  - Maryland Southern Volunteer's Song (Box 1, Item 437)
  - Maryland's Appeal (Box 1, Item 438)
  - Maryland's Lament for Jackson (Box 1, Item 439)
  - Mayor Brown (Box 1, Item 440)
  - McClellan Campaign Song (Box 1, Item 441)
  - McClellan Campaign Song (Box 1, Item 442)
  - McClellan & Victory!! (Box 1, Item 443)
  - McClellan and Victory!! (Box 1, Item 444)
  - McClellan, the Pride of "Jersey Blue." (Box 1, Item 445)
  - McClellan's Address to his Army (Box 1, Item 446)
  - M'Clellan's Band (Box 1, Item 447)
  - M'Clellan's Farewell to the Army of the Potomac (Box 1, Item 448)
  - Meeting of Old Friends (Box 1, Item 449)
  - Memories of the Past (Box 1, Item 450)
  - Merry Month of May (Box 1, Item 451)
  - Merry Month of May (Box 1, Item 452)
  - The Monitor and Merrimac (Box 1, Item 453)
  - Mother, Is the Battle Over? (Box 1, Item 454)
  - Mother, Is the Battle Over? (Box 1, Item 455)
  - Mother Kissed Me in my Dream (Box 1, Item 456)
  - Mother, I've Come Home to Die (Box 1, Item 457)
  - Mother Would Comfort Me (Box 1, Item 458)
  - Mother Would Comfort Me (Box 1, Item 459)
  - Mother Would Comfort Me (Box 1, Item 460)
  - Mother Would Wallop Me (Box 1, Item 461)
  - Mother's Waiting for her Soldier Boy (Box 1, Item 462)
  - Mother's Waiting for her Soldier Boy (Box 1, Item 463)
  - Mountaineer's Farewell or My Own Native State (Box 1, Item 464)
  - Munson's Hill! (Box 1, Item 465)
  - My God! What is all this for? (Box 1, Item 466)
  - My Love He is a Zou-Zu, Only 19 Years Old (Box 1, Item 467)
  - My Love He is a Zou-Zu Only 19 Years Old (Box 1, Item 468)
  - My Love He is a Zou-Zu Only 19 Years Old (Box 1, Item 469)
  - My Love is a Zou-Zu (Box 1, Item 470)
  - National Guard Marching Song (Box 2, Item 471)
  - National Guard's Camp Song (Box 2, Item 472)
  - National Song (Box 2, Item 473)
  - The Nation's Scourge (Box 2, Item 474)
  - National Songs (Box 2, Item 475)
  - New Hundred Years Hence (Box 2, Item 476)
  - New Red, White, and Blue (Box 2, Item 477)
  - The New Skedaddle Song (Box 2, Item 478)
  - The New Version of the Colored Volunteer (Box 2, Item 479)
  - New--York 7th Regiment (Box 2, Item 480)
  - New War Song of the 69th Regiment (Box 2, Item 481)
  - New Yankee Doodle (Box 2, Item 482)
  - New-York 12th Regiment (Box 2, Item 483)
  - New York Volunteer (Box 2, Item 484)
  - New York Volunteer (Box 2, Item 485)
  - The New-York Volunteer (Box 2, Item 486)
  - The New--York Zouaves (Box 2, Item 487)
  - 9th New-Jersey (Box 2, Item 488)
  - The Oath (Box 2, Item 489)
  - O, Lovely Dixie's Land (Box 2, Item 490)
  - Oh! Abraham, Resign! (Box 2, Item 491)
  - O, Lovely Dixie's Land (Box 2, Item 492)
  - Oh! Bless Me, Mother, Ere I Die (Box 2, Item 493)
  - Oh! I Vants to go Home (Box 2, Item 494)
  - Oh! I Wish This War Was Over (Box 2, Item 495)
  - Oh Jeff! Why Don't You Come? (Box 2, Item 496)
  - Oh Jeff! Why Don't You Come? (Box 2, Item 497)
  - Oh Jeff! Why Don't You Come? (Box 2, Item 498)
  - Old Abe Lincoln! (Box 2, Item 499)
  - Old Abe's Lament (Box 2, Item 500)
  - The Old Banner's Waving! (Box 2, Item 501)
  - The Old Contraband (Box 2, Item 502)
  - Old Jeff's Dream (Box 2, Item 503)
  - The Old Union Wagon (Box 2, Item 504)
  - Old Union Wagon (Box 2, Item 505)
  - "Ole Mose" (Box 2, Item 506)
  - On! On! On! The Boys Came Marching (Box 2, Item 507)
  - O'Toole & McFinnigan on the War (Box 2, Item 508)
  - O'Toole & McFinnigan on the War (Box 2, Item 509)
  - Our Battle-Flag (Box 2, Item 510)
  - Our Battle-Flag (Box 2, Item 511)
  - Our Beautiful Banner! (Box 2, Item 512)
  - Our Beautiful Flag (Box 2, Item 513)
  - Our Country and Flag (Box 2, Item 514)
  - Our Country's Flag (Box 2, Item 515)
  - Our Country's Flag (Box 2, Item 516)
  - Our Fifer-Boy (Box 2, Item 517)
  - Our Flag Is There (Box 2, Item 518)
  - Our Hero's Reign (Box 2, Item 519)
  - Our Marshal Kane (Box 2, Item 520)
  - Our Pottsville Volunteers (Box 2, Item 521)
  - Our Southern Dead (Box 2, Item 522)
  - Our Union (Box 2, Item 523)
  - Our Union Flag (Box 2, Item 524)
  - Our Union, Right or Wrong (Box 2, Item 525)
  - The Patriot Flag (Box 2, Item 526)
  - The Pennsylvanian Battle Cry! (Box 2, Item 527)
  - The Pennsylvanian Battle Cry! (Box 2, Item 528)
  - Picket's Last Watch (Box 2, Item 529)
  - The Poor Old Slave (Box 2, Item 530)
  - President Lincoln's Favorite Poem (Box 2, Item 531)
  - Prisoner's Hope (Box 2, Item 532)
  - "Quamdiu tandem abutere patientiae nostra?" (Box 2, Item 533)
  - Rally Around the Good Old Flag (Box 2, Item 534)
  - The Rally Cry of Freedom (Box 2, Item 535)
  - Rebel Gunpowder (Box 2, Item 536)
  - Red, White & Blue (Box 2, Item 537)
  - Remember and Repay! (Box 2, Item 538)
  - The Rebel Raid in Pennsylvania (Box 2, Item 539)
  - Remember Baltimore (Box 2, Item 540)
  - Buena Vista Guards (Box 2, Item 541)
  - Respectfully Dedicated to the True-Hearted, Brave and Patriotic Southern Girls (Box 2, Item 542)
  - Respectfully Dedicated to the True-Hearted, Brave and Patriotic Southern Girls (Box 2, Item 543)
  - The Retreat of the Grand Army from Bull Run (Box 2, Item 544)
  - Ring, Merry Bells! (Box 2, Item 545)
  - Running the Blockade Past Vicksburg (Box 2, Item 546)
  - The Satterlee Boys to Uncle Sam (Box 2, Item 547)
  - Save the Union (Box 2, Item 548)
  - Save the Union (Box 2, Item 549)
  - Scott and the Veteran (Box 2, Item 550)
  - Secessia Land (Box 2, Item 551)
  - Secession Wagon (Box 2, Item 552)
  - The Second Louisiana (Box 2, Item 553)
  - The Second Louisiana (Box 2, Item 554)
  - Seven Days Fight Before Richmond (Box 2, Item 555)
  - 79th Regiment (Box 2, Item 556)
  - Shelling Fort of Anderson (Box 2, Item 557)
  - Sheridan! Cavalry Sheridan! (Box 2, Item 558)
  - Sherman's Bonny Boys in Blue (Box 2, Item 559)
  - Sherman's March (Box 2, Item 560)
  - Sherman's March to the Sea (Box 2, Item 561)
  - Sherman's on the Track (Box 2, Item 562)
  - Sherman's on the Track (Box 2, Item 563)
  - The Shoddy Contractor (Box 2, Item 564)
  - Shoddy on the Brain (Box 2, Item 565)
  - The 69th Brigade (Box 2, Item 566)
  - 69th Regiment (Box 2, Item 567)
  - The Slain at Baltimore! (Box 2, Item 568)
  - Softly Now, Tenderly, Lift Him With Care (Box 2, Item 569)
  - A Soldier in the Colored Brigade (Box 2, Item 570)
  - The Soldier's Deathbed (Box 2, Item 571)
  - A Soldier's Dream Before a Battle (Box 2, Item 572)
  - Soldier's Friend (Box 2, Item 573)
  - The Soldier's Funeral (Box 2, Item 574)
  - Soldier's Funeral (Box 2, Item 575)
  - Soldier's Prayer (Box 2, Item 576)
  - The Soldier's Return (Box 2, Item 577)
  - The Soldier's Return to His Home (Box 2, Item 578)
  - Soldier's Sister (Box 2, Item 579)
  - Song (Box 2, Item 580)
  - A Song Dedicated to the Colored Volunteer (Box 2, Item 581)
  - A Song for Dogs (Box 2, Item 582)
  - U.S.G. A Song for the Times (Box 2, Item 583)
  - A Song for the Times, or John Brown (Box 2, Item 584)
  - A Song for the Times or John Brown (Box 2, Item 585)
  - Song for the Union Soldiers (Box 2, Item 586)
  - The Song of All Songs (Box 2, Item 587)
  - The Song of All Songs (Box 2, Item 588)
  - The Song of All Songs, No. 2 (Box 2, Item 589)
  - The Song of Company 1 (Box 2, Item 590)
  - Song of Many Songs (Box 2, Item 591)
  - Song of Many Songs (Box 2, Item 592)
  - Song of Many Songs (Box 2, Item 593)
  - Song of the Baltimore Rebels (Box 2, Item 594)
  - Song of the Baltimore Rebels (Box 2, Item 595)
  - Song of the Negro Boatman (Box 2, Item 596)
  - Song of the 214th Regt. P.V. (Box 2, Item 597)
  - Song of the Union (Box 2, Item 598)
  - Song on the Death of Col. Ellsworth (Box 2, Item 599)
  - Sons of Columbia (Box 2, Item 600)
  - The Sour Apple-Tree (Box 2, Item 601)
  - Sour Apple Tree (Box 2, Item 602)
  - South Carolina Gentleman (Box 2, Item 603)
  - Southern Battle Song (Box 2, Item 604)
  - The Southern Cross (Box 2, Item 605)
  - Southern National Song (Box 2, Item 606)
  - Southern National Song (Box 2, Item 607)
  - Southron War Song (Box 2, Item 608)
  - Southrons to Arms (Box 2, Item 609)
  - St. Patrick's Day (Box 2, Item 610)
  - Stand by the Flag (Box 2, Item 611)
  - Stand by the Union (Box 2, Item 612)
  - Star of the North (Box 2, Item 613)
  - The Stars and Bars (Box 2, Item 614)
  - Stars & Stripes (Box 2, Item 615)
  - Stars & Stripes (Box 2, Item 616)
  - The Stars & Stripes (Box 2, Item 617)
  - States' Rights Song (Box 2, Item 618)
  - The Sword and the Red White and Blue (Box 2, Item 619)
  - Lines on the Death of John Grayson (Box 2, Item 620)
  - There is Life in Old Maryland Yet (Box 2, Item 621)
  - There's a Sound Among the Forest Trees (Box 2, Item 622)
  - There's Life in the Old Land Yet (Box 2, Item 623)
  - There's Life in the Old Land Yet! (Box 2, Item 624)
  - There's Life in the Old Land Yet (Box 2, Item 625)
  - There's "No Body" Hurt!! (Box 2, Item 626)
  - They Are Coming from the Wars (Box 2, Item 627)
  - 13th Penn'a Cavalry at Fayetteville, N.C. (Box 2, Item 628)
  - Three Hundred Thousand More (Box 2, Item 629)
  - Threnody (Box 2, Item 630)
  - To My Mother (Box 2, Item 631)
  - To the Ladies of Carlisle (Box 2, Item 632)
  - To the Officers and Soldiers of the Fifth Ohio Cavalry (Box 2, Item 633)
  - Traitor, Spare that Flag (Box 2, Item 634)
  - The Triumph of the Old Flag (Box 2, Item 635)
  - The 23d Pennsylvania Volunteers in Action (Box 2, Item 636)
  - Two Years Ago (Box 2, Item 637)
  - The Tyrant's Cap (Box 2, Item 638)
  - Uncle Abe, or A Hit at the Times (Box 2, Item 639)
  - Uncle Sam's Boys (Box 2, Item 640)
  - The Union (Box 2, Item 641)
  - The Union! (Box 2, Item 642)
  - The Union! (Box 2, Item 643)
  - The Union! (Box 2, Item 644)
  - Union and Liberty (Box 2, Item 645)
  - The Union Boys (Box 2, Item 646)
  - The Union Flag Triumphant Waves (Box 2, Item 647)
  - The Union Forever! (Box 2, Item 648)
  - The Union For Ever For Me! (Box 2, Item 649)
  - The Union, It Must Be Preserved (Box 2, Item 650)
  - The Union Must and Shall be Preserved (Box 2, Item 651)
  - The Union Soldiers Address to the Flag (Box 2, Item 652)
  - The Union Soldier's Prayer (Box 2, Item 653)
  - Union Version of Maryland, My Maryland (Box 2, Item 654)
  - The Union Volunteer (Box 2, Item 655)
  - Union War Lyrics (Box 2, Item 656)
  - The Union! (Box 2, Item 657)
  - Up With the Flag, Long May it Wave! (Box 2, Item 658)
  - Up With the Red, White and Blue (Box 2, Item 659)
  - Vacant Chair (Box 2, Item 660)
  - The Vacant Chair (Box 2, Item 661)
  - Valentine & Julia (Box 2, Item 662)
  - The Veteran's Return from the War (Box 2, Item 663)
  - Victory at Last (Box 2, Item 664)
  - Vir-gin-a (Box 2, Item 665)
  - The Volunteer (Box 2, Item 666)
  - Volunteers' Song (Box 2, Item 667)
  - Volunteer's Watch Song (Box 2, Item 668)
  - Wake Nicodemus! (Box 2, Item 669)
  - The War-Christian's Thanksgiving (Box 2, Item 670)
  - The War is Over Now (Box 2, Item 671)
  - The War of 1812 & 1861 (Box 2, Item 672)
  - War Song No 2 of the 69th Regimet (Box 2, Item 673)
  - War Song of the New-York 69th Regiment (Box 2, Item 674)
  - Was My Brother in the Battle? (Box 2, Item 675)
  - Was My Brother in the Battle! (Box 2, Item 676)
  - We Are For the Union (Box 2, Item 677)
  - We Will Have the Union Still (Box 2, Item 678)
  - We Will Have the Union Still (Box 2, Item 679)
  - We Will Have the Union Still (Box 2, Item 680)
  - Welcome, Brave Boy (Box 2, Item 681)
  - Welcome Our Gallant 69th (Box 2, Item 682)
  - Welcome Our Gallant 69th (Box 2, Item 683)
  - We'll Follow the Flag (Box 2, Item 684)
  - We'll Follow the Flag (Box 2, Item 685)
  - We'll Keep Washington (Box 2, Item 686)
  - We're Marching Down to Dixie's Land (Box 2, Item 687)
  - We've a Million in the Field (Box 2, Item 688)
  - We've a Million in the Field (Box 2, Item 689)
  - Whack Row de Dow (Box 2, Item 690)
  - When Johnny Comes Marching Home (Box 2, Item 691)
  - What Irish Boys Can Do (Box 2, Item 692)
  - What Irish Boys Can Do (Box 2, Item 693)
  - When Abe Comes Marching Home Again (Box 2, Item 694)
  - When This Cruel War Is Over (Box 2, Item 695)
  - When This Cruel War Is Over (Box 2, Item 696)
  - William Price (Box 2, Item 697)
  - William Price (Box 2, Item 698)
  - A Yankee Man-of War (Box 2, Item 699)
  - Yes, I Would the War Were Over (Box 2, Item 700)
  - Yes, I Would the War Were Over (Box 2, Item 701)
  - Address of the Carrier of the Microcosm (Box 2, Item 702)
  - Alabama Waking to the Spirit of Enterprise (Box 2, Item 703)
  - Ancient Rams No. 2 of Southwark (Box 2, Item 704)
  - Arm in Arm (Box 2, Item 705)
  - Baccalaureate Poem (Box 2, Item 706)
  - The Battle Flags of Iowa (Box 2, Item 707)
  - Battle Hymn of the Republic (Box 2, Item 708)
  - Beautiful Snow (Box 2, Item 709)
  - The Bed-Bugs' Song (Box 2, Item 710)
  - Belle of Baltimore (Box 2, Item 711)
  - The Bill-Poster's Dream (Box 2, Item 712)
  - The Birds of a Feather (Box 2, Item 713)
  - Bob-Tailed Nag (Box 2, Item 714)
  - The Bold Dragoon (Box 2, Item 715)
  - Boston Tea-Party (Box 2, Item 716)
  - Boys on the Frankford Road (Box 2, Item 717)
  - Buck Goats, No. 1 (Box 2, Item 718)
  - Bull Dog an' de Baby (Box 2, Item 719)
  - Camo Kimo (Box 2, Item 720)
  - Carrier's Address to the Patrons of the Intelligence & Expositor (Box 2, Item 721)
  - Change (Box 2, Item 722)
  - Christian Experience (Box 2, Item 723)
  - The Coal Black Steed (Box 2, Item 724)
  - The Collegiad (Box 2, Item 725)
  - Colonel Clarke---a la Capt. Jinks (Box 2, Item 726)
  - Col. Clarke--a la Captian Jinks (Box 2, Item 727)
  - Columbia's Greatest Glory! (Box 2, Item 728)
  - Columbia's Greatest Glory (Box 2, Item 729)
  - The Confederate Monument (Box 2, Item 730)
  - Coon Dat Carried De Razor (Box 2, Item 731)
  - Dear Old Flag! (Box 2, Item 732)
  - The Corkers (Box 2, Item 733)
  - Dear Old Flag (Box 2, Item 734)
  - The Corkers (Box 2, Item 735)
  - The Following Lines Were Dedicated… (Box 2, Item 736)
  - Darkey Boat Glee (Box 2, Item 737)
  - De Nigger On De Fence (Box 2, Item 738)
  - De Nigger On De Fence (Box 2, Item 739)
  - De Nigger On De Fence (Box 2, Item 740)
  - De Sugar Cane Green (Box 2, Item 741)
  - The Dear Old Flag (Box 2, Item 742)
  - Dear Old Flag! (Box 2, Item 743)
  - Dearest May (Box 2, Item 744)
  - Dedication Service (Box 2, Item 745)
  - Dedicated to Joseph P. Drumm (Box 2, Item 746)
  - Los Destinos de Cuba (Box 2, Item 747)
  - Dixey's Land. No. 2 (Box 2, Item 748)
  - Dixie's Land (Box 2, Item 749)
  - Do You Ask Me If I Love You (Box 2, Item 750)
  - The Doctor's Wife (Box 2, Item 751)
  - Dupontifex Maximus (Box 2, Item 752)
  - Edgar Allan Poe (Box 2, Item 753)
  - Ella Ree (Box 2, Item 754)
  - Ella Ree (Box 2, Item 755)
  - Eulalie (Box 2, Item 756)
  - Fair Rosina (Box 2, Item 757)
  - A Family Reunion (Box 2, Item 758)
  - Few Days (Box 2, Item 759)
  - The Flower of the Land (Box 2, Item 760)
  - The Forsaken to the False One (Box 2, Item 761)
  - Franklin Hose Song (Box 2, Item 762)
  - The Fright of Old Virginia (Box 2, Item 763)
  - Full Moon Union Second Degree (Box 2, Item 764)
  - Freedom Around the Jug (Box 2, Item 765)
  - Gay Conductor (Box 2, Item 766)
  - Gentle Annie (Box 2, Item 767a)
  - Gentle Annie (Box 2, Item 767b)
  - Golden Star (Box 2, Item 768)
  - Good as Gold (Box 2, Item 769)
  - The Good Old North State (Box 2, Item 770)
  - Good Old Southern Home (Box 2, Item 771)
  - Good-Bye, Allie Dear! (Box 2, Item 772)
  - Good-Bye Liza Jane (Box 2, Item 773)
  - The Grave of Bonaparte (Box 2, Item 774)
  - The Grave of Bonaparte (Box 2, Item 775)
  - Grave of Lily Dale (Box 2, Item 776)
  - The Great Prayer (Box 2, Item 777)
  - Grecian Bend. (Box 2, Item 778)
  - Green Monsters' Song (Box 2, Item 779)
  - Greeting Song (Box 2, Item 780)
  - Gumbo Chaff (Box 2, Item 781)
  - Hail, Columbia (Box 2, Item 782)
  - Hail Columbia (Box 2, Item 783)
  - Hail Columbia (Box 2, Item 784)
  - Ham-Fat (Box 2, Item 785)
  - Happy Land of Canaan (Box 2, Item 786)
  - Harry Bluff (Box 2, Item 787)
  - The Heathen Can Be Found (Box 2, Item 788)
  - High Daddy (Box 2, Item 789)
  - High Daddy (Box 2, Item 790)
  - A Holiday Greeting (Box 2, Item 791)
  - Hop De Doodle Do (Box 2, Item 792)
  - Human Equality (Box 2, Item 793)
  - A Humble Appeal for the "Kneeling Slave" (Box 2, Item 794)
  - Hunt the Buffalo (Box 2, Item 795)
  - The Hunters of Kentucky (Box 2, Item 796)
  - Hurrah for Abe Lincoln! (Box 2, Item 797)
  - Hymn (Box 2, Item 798)
  - Hymns for the Liberator Soiree (Box 2, Item 799)
  - I Stood on the Shore (Box 2, Item 800)
  - I Stood on the Shore (Box 2, Item 801)
  - I'm Afloat (Box 2, Item 802)
  - I'm Off for Charleston (Box 2, Item 803)
  - In Memory of Everybody's Friend "Marse Jim" (Box 2, Item 804)
  - Independence Day (Box 2, Item 805)
  - The Invalid Corps (Box 2, Item 806)
  - James Abram Garfield (Box 2, Item 807)
  - Joe Bowers (Box 2, Item 808)
  - John Anderson, My Jo (Box 2, Item 809)
  - Johnny Bull and Brother Jonathan (Box 2, Item 810)
  - Johnny Is Gone for a Soldier (Box 2, Item 811)
  - The Joys of Racing (Box 2, Item 812)
  - Just As of Old (Box 2, Item 813)
  - Lincoln on a Rail (Box 2, Item 814)
  - Kemo, Kimo (Box 2, Item 815)
  - Kentucky Rose (Box 2, Item 816)
  - Klode Card (Box 2, Item 817)
  - Lazy Club (Box 2, Item 818)
  - The Leddy Macmeeken (Box 2, Item 819)
  - Lily Dale (Box 2, Item 820)
  - "Lindy" (Box 2, Item 821)
  - Long Tail Blue (Box 2, Item 822)
  - Low Back'd Car (Box 2, Item 823)
  - Maggie's Secret (Box 2, Item 824)
  - Marseilles Hymn (Box 2, Item 825)
  - Meet Me at Twilight (Box 2, Item 826a)
  - I Am Wandering All Alone (Box 2, Item 826b)
  - A la Memoria del General Lopez (Box 2, Item 827)
  - Merry Month of May (Box 2, Item 828)
  - Merry Month of May (Box 2, Item 829)
  - La Marseillaise (Box 2, Item 830)
  - Mountain Wave (Box 2, Item 831)
  - Mountain Wave (Box 2, Item 832)
  - Morir pour la Patrie! (Box 2, Item 833)
  - Mourir pour la Patrie! (Box 2, Item 834)
  - No. 3. Mrs. Cunningham's Darling Baby (Box 2, Item 835)
  - My Country 'tis of Thee (Box 2, Item 836)
  - My Dear Savannah Home (Box 2, Item 837)
  - My Own Native Land (Box 2, Item 838)
  - My Polly Ann (Box 2, Item 839)
  - My Voiceless World (Box 2, Item 840)
  - Nancy Till (Box 2, Item 841)
  - No One to Love (Box 2, Item 842)
  - Nelly Gray (Box 2, Item 843)
  - Nelly Was a Lady (Box 2, Item 844)
  - New Jers-A (Box 2, Item 845)
  - New National Hymn (Box 2, Item 846)
  - New Year's Address to the Patrons of the Anxious Seat (Box 2, Item 847)
  - Ne Plus Ultra (Box 2, Item 848)
  - Night Clubs (Box 2, Item 849)
  - Ode (Box 2, Item 850)
  - Oh! Boys, Carry me 'long (Box 2, Item 851)
  - Oh, Dem Golden Slippers (Box 2, Item 852)
  - Oh, Dem Old Brown Pants! (Box 2, Item 853)
  - Oh Susannah (Box 2, Item 854)
  - Oil on the Brain (Box 2, Item 855)
  - The Old Black Crow (Box 2, Item 856)
  - Old Bob Ridley! (Box 2, Item 857)
  - Old Cabin Home (Box 2, Item 858)
  - Old Kentucky Home (Box 2, Item 859)
  - Old Log Cabin (Box 2, Item 860)
  - Old Log Cabin in the Dell (Box 2, Item 861)
  - Old Sir Toddy (Box 2, Item 862)
  - The Original Ben Bolt (Box 2, Item 863)
  - The Original Ben Bolt (Box 2, Item 864)
  - Original Yankee Doodle (Box 2, Item 865)
  - Our Country (Box 2, Item 866)
  - Our Flag is There (Box 2, Item 867)
  - Our Flag is There (Box 2, Item 868)
  - Our Flag is There (Box 2, Item 869)
  - Our Folks (Box 2, Item 870)
  - Our Own Flag of Green (Box 2, Item 871)
  - Our Ship of State (Box 2, Item 872)
  - Our Sweethearts at Home (Box 2, Item 873)
  - The Paupers (Box 2, Item 874)
  - Philadelphia Riots (2 copies) (Box 2, Item 875a)
  - Whig Songs (2 copies) (Box 2, Item 875b)
  - Ye Soldiers of Jesus Pray (Box 2, Item 876)
  - Poor Old Uncle Rube (Box 2, Item 877)
  - Pop Goes de Weasel (Box 2, Item 878a)
  - Pop Goes the Weazle, No. 3 (Box 2, Item 878b)
  - Pop Goes the Weasel (Box 2, Item 879)
  - The Rambling Boy of Poverty (Box 2, Item 880a)
  - My Boyhood's Happy Home (Box 2, Item 880b)
  - Recording (Box 2, Item 881)
  - Ring Dat Golden Bell (Box 2, Item 882)
  - "Root Hog or Die" (Box 2, Item 883)
  - Root Hog or Die (Box 2, Item 884)
  - Root Hog or Die. No. 4 (Box 2, Item 885)
  - Sad News from Home (Box 2, Item 886)
  - "The Saddest Story Ever Told" (Box 2, Item 887)
  - The Sailor's Grave (Box 2, Item 888)
  - Scrougers' Song (Box 2, Item 889)
  - Shoo, Fly! Don't Bodder Me! (Box 2, Item 890)
  - Since I've Been in the Army (Box 2, Item 891)
  - Since I've Been in the Army (Box 2, Item 892)
  - Skidmore Guard (Box 2, Item 893)
  - The Song of Songs (Box 2, Item 894)
  - Smiggey McGuirrel (Box 2, Item 895)
  - Smiles and Kind Words (Box 2, Item 896)
  - Something to Love Me (Box 2, Item 897)
  - La Sombra de Garcia (Box 2, Item 898)
  - Something to Love Me (Box 2, Item 899)
  - Sons of Columbia (Box 2, Item 900)
  - Songs For the 4th (Box 2, Item 901a)
  - New Year's Rhymes (Box 2, Item 901b)
  - Spiritual Song (Box 2, Item 902)
  - The Star Spangled Banner (Box 2, Item 903)
  - The Starry Banner (Box 2, Item 904)
  - Stop Dat Knocking (Box 2, Item 905)
  - This Poem (Box 2, Item 906)
  - This Song for Sale (Box 2, Item 907)
  - To Whom it May Concern (Box 2, Item 908)
  - To Ireland! (Box 2, Item 909)
  - To My Wife (Box 2, Item 910)
  - Reverend John Lind (Box 2, Item 911)
  - Uncle Ned (Box 2, Item 912)
  - Unfurl the Stars and Stripes (Box 2, Item 913)
  - Unfurl the Stars and Stripes (Box 2, Item 914)
  - Uncle Sam's Farm (Box 2, Item 915)
  - Uncle Snow (Box 2, Item 916)
  - Union Republican Campaign Song (Box 2, Item 917)
  - The Unknown Grave (Box 2, Item 918)
  - The Veteran's Cross of Honor (Box 2, Item 919)
  - The Veterans of the South (Box 2, Item 920)
  - Vive l'America (Box 2, Item 921)
  - The War in Europe (Box 2, Item 922)
  - Wayfaring Stranger (Box 2, Item 923)
  - We Met by Chance (Box 2, Item 924)
  - Will You Come? (Box 2, Item 925)
  - Willie We Have Missed You (Box 2, Item 926)
  - Written and Sold for the Benefit of Matthias Lopez (Box 2, Item 927)
  - Written by James R. Thomas, Give What You Please For This (Box 2, Item 928)
  - Written on the Occasion of the President's Veto of the Inflation Bill (Box 2, Item 929)
  - Softly Now, Tenderly, Lift Him With Care (Box 2, Item 930)
  - Old Union Wagon (Box 2, Item 931)
  - Mother, I've Come Home to Die (Box 2, Item 932)
  - My Love is on the Battle Field (Box 2, Item 933)
  - The Flag with the Thirty-Four Stars (Box 2, Item 934)
  - The Flag with the Thirty-Four Stars (Box 2, Item 935)
  - Parody On When This Cruel War Is Over (Box 2, Item 936)
  - No News for Me (Box 2, Item 937)